Here's something most people don't
think about before a project kickoff
meeting:
the employer is evaluating you.
Not formally, not with a rubric.
But they're forming an impression.
Did this team prepare?
Do they understand what we do?
Are they going to need
hand-holding, or can I trust them to
run with this?
That impression gets set fast, often
in the first ten minutes.
And it shapes everything that
follows.
Teams that come across as prepared
and attentive get more autonomy,
more access, and more candid
answers.
Teams that show up cold may get
managed more tightly, sometimes
for the rest of the project.
The good news is that the bar isn't
perfection. It's preparation.
Knowing what the organization
does, having specific questions
ready, and listening carefully enough
to ask a follow-up that shows you
understood what was said.
That's what separates a team an
employer wants to work with from
one they feel they have to supervise.
Your job in this meeting isn't to
present or impress.
It's to understand.
But how well you understand will
tell your employer a lot about what
kind of team you are.