Here's something worth knowing.
Two years ago, most professionals outside of tech had never used
an AI tool at work. Today, the majority have.
That's not a gradual trend.
That's one of the fastest shifts in how professional work gets done
that we've ever seen. And it's not just the obvious roles.
Yes, software engineers use AI to write code.
But so do grant writers drafting funding proposals, urban planners
modeling neighborhood impact, journalists fact-checking across
thousands of public records, and HR teams rethinking how they
write job descriptions. AI didn't just show up in tech.
It showed up everywhere, quickly. Here's why that matters for you.
Employers are already adjusting their expectations.
The ability to work effectively with AI tools is becoming a baseline
professional skill, the way spreadsheet literacy or business writing
were for previous generations. Not "nice to have." Expected.
That doesn't mean you need to become a technical expert.
It means you need to understand what these tools can and can't
do, know when to use them and when to set them aside, and be
able to explain and stand behind any work they helped you
produce.
That's exactly what the AI modules in this course are designed to
build. This isn't a sidebar topic.
It's one of the most directly career-relevant skills you'll practice
here.