This course works differently than what you're probably used to.
Here's what to expect.
You'll work on a real project for a real organization, as part of a
team.
The people you're delivering to aren't grading you on a rubric.
They have an actual need for what you produce.
That changes the stakes. There are no exams. No final papers.
You're assessed on the work you create, the professional skills you
demonstrate, and your ability to reflect on your own growth.
The artifacts you produce and the thinking behind them are what
matter. AI is part of the process here.
You'll learn how to use it as a professional tool. More on that soon.
You won't get all the content up front and apply it at the end.
Instead, you'll pick up new skills and frameworks along the way,
right when you need them for the work you're doing that week.
And there are regular checkpoints built in throughout the course to
help you stay on track.
You're not on your own until the final deadline.
It might feel unfamiliar at first.
There's no single right answer, and your team is counting on you to
show up and contribute.
That's what professional work actually looks like.
Learning to navigate it is one of the most valuable things you'll take
from this course.