This course doesn't work like most of your other classes.
There are no exams. No lectures to sit through.
Instead, you'll work on a real project for a real organization, as part
of a team.
That might sound exciting, or it might sound a little intimidating.
Either way, it's worth understanding why the course is built this
way. The professional world runs on projects.
Teams form, figure out a problem together, deliver something, and
move on to the next one.
The skills that matter most in that context, things like
communication, collaboration, critical thinking, those don't
develop from reading about them.
They develop from doing them, reflecting on what happened, and
trying again. That's what experiential learning is.
You learn by doing real work, not simulated work.
And because the project is real, the stakes feel different.
Your employer contact is a real person.
Your deliverables will be used.
The feedback you get is professional feedback.
This week is your on-ramp. No team yet, no project yet.
Just the foundations you'll need once both arrive.
Take your time with it.
Everything you encounter this week will show up again later in the
course.