Think about the best professional you know.
Maybe it's a manager, a mentor, someone you've worked with.
What makes them good at what they do?
Chances are, it's not just that they have the right skills.
It's that they've learned from experience in a way that most people
don't.
They can tell you exactly what they'd do differently if they could
run a meeting again, or why their approach to a particular problem
changed after seeing it go wrong the first time.
That's reflective practice.
It's the difference between having ten years of experience and
having one year of experience ten times.
In this course, you'll use a model called DEAL.
Describe what happened. Examine why it happened the way it did.
Then articulate what you learned and how you'll use it going
forward. It sounds straightforward, and it is, but it takes practice.
Most people skip straight from "what happened" to "what I'll do
next" without spending any time on the examine step, the part
where the real insight lives.
You'll complete several DEAL reflections throughout this course.
Each one builds on the last.
By the end, you'll have a portfolio that shows not just what you did,
but what you learned from doing it.
That's the kind of evidence that stands out in a job interview or a
performance review.