Being good with AI doesn't mean using it for everything.
It means knowing how to use it well.
Here's what that looks like in practice.
A marketing manager uses AI to draft three different angles for a
campaign pitch, then picks the strongest one and rewrites it in her
voice.
A consultant asks AI to summarize a hundred pages of industry
reports, then spends an hour verifying the key claims before
putting them in front of a client.
A project lead uses AI to stress-test a project timeline, asking "what
could go wrong with this plan?" before presenting it to
stakeholders.
None of these people are handing their work over to AI.
They're using it to think faster, explore more options, and catch
things they might miss. Then they apply their own judgment.
Here's why this matters.
In a professional setting, you own what you submit.
If a client asks you to explain a finding in your report and you can't
because AI generated it and you never really understood it, that's a
problem. Not a policy problem. A credibility problem.
The skills on this page will help you avoid that.
You'll learn how to prompt AI so it gives you something useful, and
how to evaluate what it gives you so you're never caught off guard.